There are many terms and conditions in the insurance of this vehicle,
but when
we take insurance, no one looks at it carefully
and at the time of making a claim,
your claim gets rejected for it,
so today we will generally discuss some important reaction divisions for our two wheeler and
private car,
so let's start
why a vehicle claim gets rejected, the
first reason is Delhi Driving License,
friends, you must always get a driving license before driving a vehicle
and
that too about the right option class, meaning two wheeler wala
for two wheeler and
courier wala deal for four wheeler and about which
deal is required for driving which vehicle, I have
already made a video about it, you will find its link
in the description and in the i button,
now definitely check it,
whenever your vehicle meets with an accident
and you get an ATM done or register it,
before that
definitely check your driving license because at the
time of registration, the ATM
asks you for the name of the driver and it gets
registered, it cannot be changed later
and if that driving license is not yours then
you do not get time and
if it is not known even at the time of verification  It is said
that if the driver does
not have a driving license, then there is a reaction in the film. The
second is that I get excited and registration
means that you are driving the car without registration. This does
not happen much right now because right now
whenever you buy a new car from the showroom, you will be
able to take out the car only after registration. But still there is a little bit of a case
that if you buy a new car from the showroom
and have not got it registered and are
driving the car on the road, then if a correction is made then
you do not get the claim. So whenever you
buy a new car, first get it registered and then
drive the car on the road.
Next is the suspension of driving license and
registration certificate. This means that if the
RTO catches you or the traffic police
catches you for something, they put a check on you and at
that time
they cancel or suspend your driving license or registration. At that
time,
never drive the car. If you have an
account while driving and you love
and the insurance companies
check the documents and it shows suspended then
you do not get the claim. So if your
driving license or registration certificate is suspended then never
drive the car.
Next is the suspension of driving license and registration certificate.  I've already made a detailed video about the Suntan Free in Seoul City,
meaning a no-claim bonus.
You'll find a link to that as well. Please check it out.
If you don't take the insurance in a particular year,
you
get a discount on your insurance premium the following year.
What happens sometimes is that you take the insurance premium
and then you say you haven't
taken it, and for whatever reason, if you take it, then that insurance also has a
penalty at that time. If
you click on it, and it's an antibiotic, the
insurance company can also charge you at that time,
or make some deductions.
It's different from that. So,
never give a false NCP declaration.
Next is the delay in flame intimation.
Whenever there's an accident in literature and old images, file a
film immediately. If you
click on it after a long time, the
insurance company can reject your claim.
When the damage to your vehicle becomes old
and straight, it becomes clear
that you've been there for a long time.  Even if there is damage,
insurance companies can make a no claim claim,
but if there is any reason for you
like you are hospitalized or the vehicle
is in a major accident and is in the police station, then on all these
reasons there can be a delay in claim intimation, have you
heard of it, but now try to get it
registered as soon as possible.
Next commercial, in that of 15th,
many people, in order to save permit and tax,
give the vehicle on rent but
keep it with private registration or
some people give it at a very low rate and
use it for private use, give it on
rent at times and that too with private
registration, so if at any time your
vehicle met with an accident at the time of rent
and the insurance company came to know that
someone was taking the vehicle on rent, then your
claim gets rejected.
Next multiple images,
multiple images means whenever you
drive the vehicle in the market, till now you have
subscribed, got the website done, got the right
side done, got it done in the future also and like this,
if you
do all the infections simultaneously for a year, then the insurance
company does not give it because it does
not have the vision.  It happens because it does not happen all at once
because in insurance you get only the
loss that happens at one time, so
if your car gets damaged anywhere, then get it insured
immediately because
if you do all the work all at once, then it can be done
without the insurance company.
So in this video we have discussed the basic things that are
required for driving a car or for making a claim.
If you liked this video, then definitely like and share it
because other people should also know this
and if you want similar information video
recording of the car, then
definitely subscribe to this channel. Thank you.